（忆往昔）
晚安 宝贝
Good night, love.
做个好梦 萨姆
Sweet dreams, Sam.
萨姆 你是我最喜爱的
Sammy, you're my favorite.
你是说我体内流着魔鬼的血？
Does this mean I have demon blood in me?
是你
It's you. Ah!
玛丽
Mary!
你看 我们的一生都用来搜寻这个恶魔
look, our whole lives have been searching for this demon.
那东西杀死了杰西 杀死了妈妈
that thing killed jess!that thing killed mom!
萨姆
sam…
我很抱歉
i'm sorry.
为了什么
for what?
你是谁 卡西迪奥
who are you?castiel.
我是那个紧紧抓住你的人
i'm the one who gripped you tight.
带你出地狱
and raised you from perdition.
- 我意思是 你是什么 - 我是伺奉主的天使
i mean, what are you?i'm an angel of the lord.
- 萨缪尔 库尔特打造了一把特别的枪.这把枪能杀死任何的东西
- samuel colt made a special gun.this gun can kill anything.
为什么一个天使要救我出地狱？
why would an angel rescue me from hell?
因为这是主的命令
because god commanded it.
因为我们有任务交给你
because we have work for you.
准备好了？
ready?
当然
definitely.
嘿 迪恩
hello, Dean.
你梦到了些什么？
and what were you dreaming about?
- 你有窥视别人睡觉的怪癖吗？
- you get your freak on by watching other people sleep?
你想干嘛？
what do you want?
听着
listen to me.
你必须阻止它
you have to stop it.
阻止什么？
stop what?
醒醒 伙计
move it, buddy.
你不能睡在这儿
you can't sleep here.
知道了
okay.
我睡在哪儿？
sleep where?
哪里都行就是不能在这儿
anywhere but here.
真有一套
perfect.
嘿 我这是在哪儿？
hey, where the hell am i?
杰伊小鸟餐馆
jay bird's diner.
嗯 谢谢 不过我意思是 哪座城市 哪个州
yeah, thanks.i mean, uh, city and state.
劳伦斯 堪萨斯
lawrence, kansas.
劳伦斯
lawrence.
你还好吗 伙计？
are you okay, buddy?
还行
yeah.
疯狂之夜
tough night.
嘿 瑞奇 来一杯咖啡
hey, uh, coffee here, reg.
你能告诉我哪里可以接收到手机信号呢？
can you tell me where I can get reception on this thing?
国家军工厂？
the u.s.s. enterprise?
谢谢
thanks.
好主意
nice threads.
你知道桑尼和雪儿分手了吧？
you know sonny and cher broke up, right?
桑尼和雪儿分手？
sonny and cher broke up?
- 嘿 温切斯特！
- hey, winchester!
- 你这家伙！你在这儿干嘛 下士？
- son of a bitch! how you doin', corporal?
- 你好 D先生 - 我听说你回来了
- hey, mr. d. - I heard you were back.
- 是的 刚回来不久
- yeah, a little while now.
你回来了就好 约翰-真他妈的好
good to have you home, john - - damn good.
老爸？
dad?
- 代我向你老爸为好 - 好的 D先生
- say hello to your old man for me.-you got it, mr. d.
我们认识吗？
do we know each other?
我想不认识的
i guess not.
轻松点 朋友
take it easy, pal.
好的
yeah.
[邪恶力量 第4季第2集]
这是要干嘛？
what is this?
你认为这像是要干嘛？
what does it look like?
- 这一切是真的 - 千真万确
- is it real? - very.
是吗 天使也生产时空飞车（来自电影《回到未来》）？
okay, so, what, angels got their hands on some deloreans?
我怎么到这儿的？
how did I get here?
时空是可以变换的 迪恩
time is fluid, Dean.
虽然这并不容易 但我们偶尔是可以曲扭时空的
it's not easy, but we can bend it on occasion.
那好 把它扭回去 要不就告诉这我该死的在这儿究竟做什么？
well, bend it back. or tell me what the hell i'm doing here.
我告诉过你了
i told you.
你必须阻止它
you have to stop it.
阻止什么？嗯？
stop what? huh?
究竟是什么 是我老爸有危险吗？
what, is there something nasty after my dad?
拜托
come on.
你就不能好好回答问题吗 你这个混蛋！
what, are you allergic to straight answers, you son of a bitch?!
好吧 年轻人看你是第一次买车
fine young man like yourself just starting out.
我再给你优惠250美元如何？
how about I take off another $250?
成交
let's do it.
我先去处理手续
i'll get the paperwork.
那可不是你想要的
that's not the one you want.
你跟踪我？
you following me?
不 不 我只是刚好路过
no, no.i was just passing by.
我还没感谢你今天早上请我喝的那杯咖啡
i never got to thank you for that cup of coffee this morning.
我当时有点冒犯了
i was a little out of it.
是有点
more than a little.
让我弥补一下
let me repay the favor.
这才是你想要的车
this is the car you want.
是吗 你对车很有研究吗
oh, yeah? you know something about cars?
是的
yeah.
是的 我父亲教我的
yeah, my dad taught me everything I know.
这是辆好车
and this… this is a great car.
327四腔 275匹马力
327 four-barrel, 275 horses.
破是破了点 但绝对是个宝
a little tlc, this thing is cherry.
老兄啊
you know, man…
你说得对
you're right.
你买刚刚那个干什么啊
what are you buying that thing for?
我答应别人要买的
kind of promised someone I would.
连67年的雪佛兰也比不上吗
over a '67 chevy?
得了吧 这是千载难逢的好车
i mean, come on.this is the car of a lifetime.
相信我 那辆车就是在40年代也很不济
trust me, this thing's still gonna be badass when it's 40.
我叫约翰 温彻斯特
john winchester.
谢谢
thanks.
我是迪恩 范 海伦（电影里的驱魔人）
Dean van halen.
谢谢你了
and thank you.
今早我有些莽撞吧
i was in pretty rough shape this morning, huh?
你也知道啊
no kidding.
我以前也试过宿醉
i've been hung over before, but, hey,
那快餐店实在令人心寒
i was getting chills in that diner.
你不觉得发寒吧 是吗
you didn't feel any of those cold spots, did you?
没有
nope.
no.
我确定 我闻到了奇怪的气味
i swore I smelled something weird, too, you know?
像臭鸡蛋味
like rotten eggs.
你不会碰巧闻到硫磺的味道吧
you didn't happen to smell any sulfur, by chance?
没
no.
没有
这小镇有牲口离奇死亡吗
have there been any cattle mutilations in town?
好了 老兄 别问了
okay, mister, stop it.
好的
yeah.
如果我能找到对策的话
if only I knew what to stop.
听我说…你自己要万事小心 好吗
listen, uh…watch out for yourself, okay?
好的 当然
yeah. sure.
怎么样
so?
我买这辆
i'll take this one.
这是怎么回事
what's this?
我的新车
my car.
那辆有蓬货车怎么不好了
what happened to the van?
玛丽 这比那辆货车好多了
mary, this is better than the van.
它有327四腔汽化器
it's got a 327, a 4-barrel carburetor.
妈妈
mom.
萨姆 无论你在哪里
sammy, wherever you are…
记住妈妈是个美女
mom is a babe.
我要下地狱了
i'm going to hell.
再一次
again.
我应该跟他谈谈
i should just talk to him.
我爸就那样 约翰 他和你不同
my dad's being my dad, john.it's not you.
为什么和我不同 他这样都几年了
how is it not me?he's been like this for how many years?
他只是太过爱护我罢了
he's just protective over me, that's all.
他不想我…
he's doesn't want me to…
和机械工家和技工儿子交往吗
hook up with a mechanic from a family of mechanics?
不是
no.
我就喜欢你现在这样
i love you for exactly what you are.
我去去就回
i'll be right back.
你怎么老跟着我们
why are you following us?
你疯了吗
are you crazy?
你从我家跟踪我们到这里
you've been trailing us since my house.
- 我不知道你瞎扯什么 - 是吗
i don't know what you're talking about.oh, really?
好吧 现在我们可以谈谈
okay, how about we talk about this, huh?
放开我
let me go!
你也是猎手吗
are you a hunter?
晚点见
see you later?
看你有没有运气吧
if you're lucky.
迪恩 是吧
Dean, right?
我真不知道要不要让你进来
i'm not sure you should come in.
你可以相信我
you can trust me.
我是说 我们都是本行 是吧
i mean, come on, we're all hunters, right?
事实上 俺们还是一家人
i mean, we're - - we're practically family.
问题是 我爸 他有点…
the thing is, my dad, he's a little, um…
我更要会会他
oh, i got to meet him.
你认识他？
you've heard of him?
百闻不如一见
clearly, not enough.
那么说 你是猎手了
so, you're a hunter?
告诉我猎手先生
well, tell me something, Mr. Hunter.
你是用木桩还是银匕首杀死吸血鬼
you kill vampires with wooden stakes or silver?
都不是 直接把头剁下来
neither.you cut their heads off.
我通过你的考验了吗
so, do I pass your test?
是的
yep.
现在你可以走人了
now get out of my house.
爸
dad!
我不相信别的猎手 迪恩
i don't trust other hunters, Dean.
不需他们的支援
don't want their help.
不需要他们介入我的家庭
don't want them around my family.
得了吧 萨缪尔
knock it off, samuel.
他是个猎手
he's a hunter.
他也通过了你的快问快答测试
who passed your little pop quiz,
我打算留他下来共进晚餐
and now i'm inviting him to dinner.
- 你饿吗 - 快饿晕了
you hungry?starving.
好极了
good.
我是迪安娜
i'm Deanna.
我的丈夫萨缪尔 你也知道的
you've met my husband, samuel.
现在快去洗手吧
now wash up.
萨缪尔和…迪安娜？
samuel and…Deanna?
真的吗
really?
第一次来劳伦斯吗 迪恩
first time in lawrence, Dean?
以前来过
well…been a while.
想必这里也人事几番新了
things sure have changed…i think.
你有任务在身吗
you working a job?
是的 可能有
yeah, ybe.
什么意思
what's that mean?
意思是 我也不轻易相信别的猎手 萨缪尔
it means I don't trust other hunters either, samuel.
为什么你要跟踪我和约翰
so, why were you following me and john?
我以为有些鬼魂盯上了你…男朋友
i thought something was after your - - your boyfriend.
但是 我弄错了
but, um, i don't think that anymore.
约翰 温彻斯特被鬼魂缠上了
john winchester mixing it up with spirits.
难以想象吧
can you imagine?
又来了
i saw that.
什么
what?
那个酸巴巴的样子
that sour-lemon look.
慢着
now, hold on.
约翰真的是和很好的…
john's a really, really nice…
淳朴良民
…naive civilian.
又如何 你宁愿我和这样的人一起吗
so, what, would you rather me be with a guy like this?
什么 不 不
what? no, no.
玛丽 我不是那个意思 我只是…
mary, of course not.it's just that I - -
你们两个说够了 我们还有客人呢
that's enough, both of you.we have company.
那么 你呢 萨穆 也有任务吗
so, what about you, sam?you, uh, working a job?
可能吧
might be.
他在韦特夏尔农场工作
he's working a job on the whitshire farm.
韦特夏尔 这听起来怎么这么像我的名字
whitshire - - why does that name sound familiaro me?
这白色黑字上有 汤姆 韦特夏尔
it's been all over the papers tom whitshire.
一些附近的镇子都联合起来
got tangled up in a combine a few towns over.
这类事情常发生
that kind of thing happens.
除了为什么他准备在第一现场动手
except why was he on it in the first place.
当他的农作物都枯萎的时候？
when his crops arare all dead?
恶魔的预兆
demonic omens?
这正是我设法想查出来的东西
that's what I got to find out.
镇上其他地方呢
what about the rest of the town?
你在网上有查到什么吗
did you find anything on the web?
那些…信息 你搜集到吗
of…information that you have assembled?
可能是电能风暴吧
electrical storms, maybe.
气象图应该在星期五就能拿到
the weather service graphs should be here on friday.
用邮递
by mail?
不是 昨晚我们租了一架飞机 让他们载过来
no, we hired a jetliner to fly them to us overnight.
你知道的 这听起来
you know, it sounds to me.
我们像是在猎同一样东西
like we might be hunting the same thing.
你知道的 如果我们能多点人一起去
you know, if we go in there in numbers,
相互间就能得到很好的照应
we'll take care of this real quick.
你不知道什么叫「我们各自为战」么 孩子
what part of "we work alone"do you not understand, son?
我之所以在这里是因为…
and i'm here because…
家族事业 玛莉
family business, mary.
家族
family.
你宁愿在一群大学运动员当中当啦啦队吗
what, you'd rather be waving pom-poms at a bunch of dumb jocks?
你去哪
uh, where you going?
去干活了 老爸
to do the job, dad.
神父
father.
你在这里真让我吃惊
i see you beat me here.
主也挺幽默的
the lord is funny that way.
贝丝 韦特夏尔
beth whitshire…
这是我的助手
this is my associate,
我们年长的牧师 切尼神父
our senior senior priest, father cheney.
我代表教区
please accept our deepest condolences.
致以我们最衷心的哀悼
on behalf of the county diocese.
谢谢
thank you.
韦特夏尔夫人刚告诉了我关于汤姆的一切
miss whitshire was just telling me all about tom.
还提起了他死前
and how normal and ordinary things were.
所发生的一些事
on the day before his death.
了解
i see.
那你真的没注意到有特别的地方吗 夫人
so you didn't notice anything unusual, ma'am?
你的意思是我丈夫的精力突然恢复到40岁的样子？
you mean like my husband's guts fertilizing the back 40?
失陪了
excuse me.
查理 你能告诉神父
charlie, would you like to tell the father here.
刚刚你对我说的话吗
what you just told me?
爸爸有时候喝醉了
dad drank sometimes.
有时候 他对妈妈很粗暴
sometimes he got rough with mom.
就在那时 一个陌生人进来了
and that's when the stranger came?
我以为他只是个传教士
i just thought he was some bible-thumper,
像你那样
like you-all.
他在一个星期前曾出现过
he showed up about a week ago.
说了什么
saying what?
问我想不想阻止这些暴力
did I want the beatings to stop?
当时我只认为他是个疯子 我没想到
i just thought he was crazy.i didn't think.
之后 爸爸死了
and the next thing I know, dad's dead.
我要去蹲监狱吗
am I going to jail?
不需要 查理
you didn't do this, charlie.
那个陌生人有没有索要什么作为回报
did the stranger want something in return?
他什么都不要
he didn't want anything.
拜托 查克 他不会白施舍人的
come on, chuck.he wasn't just handing out freebies, now, was he?
他确实说了什么未来的召唤
he did say something about coming a-calling.
从现在起10年内
10 years from now.
他可能会有想要的东西
and maybe he'd want something then.
一些什么东西
something like what?
我不知道 这行了吧
i don't know, okay?
听着 我告诉你了 他是个疯子
look, i told you he was nuts.
你怎么想
what do you think?
我想他刚把灵魂出卖给了恶魔
i think he just pimped his soul to a demon,
他对此一无所知
and he doesn't even know it.
查理 你记得那陌生人长什么样的
charlie, do you remember what the stranger looked like?
记得
yeah, uh…
他大概5尺10寸 白人
he's about 5'10"… white.
他是那种看上去很正常的人 真的
he was kind of normal-looking, really.
还有什么吗
anything else?
的确有一样很特别 什么
there was one thing.what?
就是他的眼 他的眼球很怪异
it's just, the light hit his eyes in a weird way, and…
有一阵子 我发誓
for a moment, i could have sworn - -
不
no.
是黄色的
they were yellow.
暗黄色
pale yellow.
我们慢慢来 把事情整理一遍
what do you say we just slow down and talk this thing through?
没什么可说的
there's nothing to talk about.
除了你说有个恶魔
except you're saying there's a demon,
而且我们都没听说过黄眼睛的恶魔
and none of us has ever heard of demon with yellow eyes.
可是我见过
yeah, well, i have.
这东西杀了我全家
this thing killed my family.
- 冷静 - 你不明白
- just calm down, son. - you don't get it, do you?
你现在很危险 我们都处于危险之中
you are in danger. we are all in danger.
你应该为自己找个安全的地方
in fact, you need to get yourself someplace safe.
但得先让我知道我们对付的是什么
not until we know what we're dealing with here.
萨姆是对的 迪恩 它可能是恶魔
sam's right, Dean. it could be a demon,
也可能是无形人 或是其它什么东西
it could be a shapeshifter, any number of things.
我知道它是什么
i know what this thing is!
我会杀了它
and i'm gonna kill it.
这就是我想说的
that's all the talking I need to do.
你要杀一个恶魔 怎么杀
you're gonna kill a demon? how?
有个叫丹尼尔·艾金斯的猎人
there's a hunter named daniel elkins.
他住在科罗拉多 他有把库尔特手枪
He lives in colorado. He has coIt's gun.
库尔特手枪
the colt.
我倒是听说过库尔特手枪
yeah, i heard about the colt.
我曾把它当作睡前故事讲给玛丽听
i used to tell it to mary as a bedtime story.
但这是真的
well, it's real.
好吧 就算是真的
all right, say that it is.
你难道有颗水晶球
you got some kind of a crystal ball.
能告诉你恶魔会出现在哪吗？
telling you where this demon's gonna be?
也许我就是有
yeah, maybe I do.
- 这是什么 - 一份笔记
- what's this? - it's a list.
什么的笔记
of what?
我父亲写下了所有与黄眼睛恶魔
my dad wrote down anyone he thought ever came in contact.
接触时的信息 包括时间 地点 人物
with the yellow-eyed demon. who, where, and when.
但是为什么呢
why?
因为他对那恶魔有越多的了解
'cause the more he could learn about the son of a bitch,
他就越有可能弄清楚为什么它杀死我母亲
the more he could figure out why it killed my mom.
看
look.
韦特夏尔农场
whitshire farm.
我说过这名字听着耳熟
i told you that name sounded familiar.
韦特夏尔农场 那可是两天前
whitshire farms - - that was two days ago.
这怎么会在你父亲的笔记上
how the hell is that on your dad's list?
我父亲能预见未来
my dad could see the future.
看这儿 说它明晚会袭击那儿
look at this - - says he's gonna hit here tomorrow night.
丽迪·沃尔什
liddy walsh?
海利镇
haleyville.
那里很近
that's close.
只有3英里 但是…
yeah, it's about 3 miles, but…
我知道你们认为我疯了
i know you guys think i'm crazy.
你看着是个不错的小伙 但是你疯了
you seem like a really nice kid, Dean, but, yeah, you're crazy.
是的 也许吧
yeah, maybe.
但是我知道这混蛋要去哪
but I know where this bastard's gonna be.
而我要阻止它
and i'm gonna stop it…
杀了它一劳永逸
once and for all.
我要出发了
i, uh, i'm shoving off.
我只是来说声再见
i just wanted to say "bye."
是吗
really?
那么快
so soon?
是啊 有工作要做
yeah, i have a job to do.
我想告诉你
hey, i wanted to tell you,
你要记住
you know, for what it's worth, um…
你父亲的想法并不那么重要
it doesn't matter what your dad thinks.
我喜欢约翰
i like that john kid.
是吗
you do?
是的
yeah.
我认为你们俩注定是一对
yeah, i think you two are meant to be.
我就指望你们了
hell, i'm depending on it.
- 什么 - 没什么
- what? - nothing.
我能问你个问题吗
can I ask you a question?
约翰他是怎样的人
what's he like - - john?
为什么这么问
why do you ask?
只是好奇心而已
just curious.
让我想想
i don't know.
他很贴心
he's sweet…
很友善
kind.
即使在战后 在一切都过去之后
even after the war, after everything,
他仍然相信「幸福终局」这样的电影
he still believes in "happily ever after, " you know?
他有着猎人所没有的东西
he's everything a hunter isn't.
没有冒犯你的意思
no offense.
没什么
no, none taken.
能跟你说件事吗
can I tell you something?
他快要向我求婚了
he's gonna ask me to marry him.
我想就在明天
tomorrow, i think.
是吗
yeah?
老爸肯定会气爆的
oh, dad's gonna explode.
但我不在意
but I don't care.
有必要的话我就私奔
i'll run away if I have to.
我只是…
i just…
我爱约翰
i love john.
而且
and…
而且什么
and what?
我不想干了
i want to get out.
这样的工作 这样的生活
this job, this life…
我恨这一切
i hate it.
我想要一个家庭
i want a family.
我想要有安全感
i want to be safe.
我能想像到的最糟糕的事情
you know, the worst thing I can think of…
最最糟糕的事情
the very worst thing…
就是我的孩子像我一样长大
is for my children to be raised into this, like I was.
我不会让这发生
well, i won't let it happen.
是啊
yeah.
你还好吗
you okay?
是的 我很好
yeah. no, i'm - - i'm fine.
玛丽
uh, mary…
我能跟你说件事吗
can I tell you something?
当然
sure.
即使这听起来很奇怪
even if this sounds really weird,
你能答应我把它记住吗
will you promise me that you will remember?
好的
okay.
到1983年11月2日那天
on november 2, 1983…
千万别下床
…don't get out of bed.
无论你听见或看见什么
no matter what you hear or what you see…
答应我千万别下床
…promise me you won't get out of bed.
好的
okay.
那就好
上帝是我的副驾驶 是吗
so, what, god's my co-pilot? is that it?
你是一个普通爱说闲话的小孩
oh, you're a regular chatty cathy.
跟我说说看
tell me something.
萨姆很想知道这些
sam would have wanted in on this.
为什么不把他带回来
why not bring him back?
你得自己完成 迪恩
you had to do this alone, Dean.
你也不必担心他正在揭开的未来
and you don't care that he's tearing up the future.
现在找我
looking for me right now?
萨姆没有找你
sam's not looking for you.
好吧 如果我这么做了
all right,
if I do this,
那个家庭的诅咒就被解除了对吧
then the family curse breaks, right?
爸爸妈妈就幸福的生活下去了
mom and dad live happily ever after,
萨姆和我快乐成长
and sam and I grow up.
玩着老鹰捉小鸡游戏
playing little league and chasing tail?
你要意识到如果你这么做了
you realize if you do alter the future,
你父亲 你 萨姆 你们永远不会变成猎手了
your father, you, sam, you'll never become hunters.
所有你救过的人都会死去
and all those people you saved, they'll die.
我明白
i realize.
你不在乎吗
and you don't care?
我在乎
oh, i care.
我非常在乎
i care a lot.
但他们是我父母
but these are my parents.
我不会让他们再次死去
i'm not gonna let them die again.
绝不能
i can't.
不会的 如果我能阻止他们
not if I can stop it.
哥们 站那儿别动
hold it right there, friend.
把枪放下
drop the gun.
忙你自己的事去吧
be on your way.
我不能这么做 丹尼尔
can't do it, daniel.
你他妈是谁啊
who the hell are you?
也和你们一样是个猎人
a hunter, just like yourself.
或者说小偷更合适
"thief" is more like it.
我只是借用几天而已
i just need itfor a few days.
不会再发生了 先生
not happening, mister.
瞧 我现在有机会拯救我的家庭
look, i have a chance to save my family's lives.
我的家庭
my family.
但我需要这把枪帮我
but I need this gun to do it.
如果你要阻止我那你杀了我得了
so if you want to stop me, kill me.
在劳伦斯还有些猎手 坎贝尔一家
there's some hunters in lawrence the campbells.
从没听说过
never heard of them.
她会在那里出现
that's where she'll be.
迪恩说他会去哪
Dean say where he was going?
他说他去杀恶魔了
he said he was gonna kill a demon.
杀恶魔
kill a demon?
不可能
that's impossible.
是呀
yep.
在哪儿
where?
我不清楚哎 在海利镇那边吧
oh, i don't know over in haleyville.
可能在沃尔什
uh, walshes, maybe.
等下 不是丽迪·沃尔什
oh, wait - - not liddy walsh?
这个 我估计是
well, yeah, i-i think so.
爸爸 她是我的朋友
dad, she's a friend of mine!
我们要去帮她
we got to help her.
怎么了
what's wrong?
我在车里等你
i'll be in the car.
嗨
hey!
她想去捕猎 她不想去捕猎
she wants to hunt, she doesn't want to hunt.
这是一些女人每月必修之事吗
is this some female "time of month" thing?
什么
what?
抱歉 丽迪
i'm sorry, liddy.
转移了已经
it's metastasized.
去哪了
where?
他的肺 他的肝
his liver, his lungs.
我们该谈谈条件了
it's time we talked about arrangements.
别啊 你应该做点什么 布朗医生
no, you have to do something, dr. brown.
确实有个办法可以治疗
there is one way a cure, actually.
但我需要你的帮助
but i'll need your help.
让我做什么
what do I have to do?
没什么
nothing.
但未来10年内我会去找你
just in 10 years, i'm going to come to you.
问你要点东西的
and ask for something then.
什么
what?
你不会错过的
nothing you'll miss.
记着啊
hold that thought.
你个混蛋
you son of a bitch.
你好
well, hello, there.
他们把你藏哪了
where the hell have they been hiding you?
我喜欢你
i like you.
你很勇敢
you got a lot of spunk.
放她走
you let her go!
你从哪拿到枪的
where'd you get that gun?
玛丽 他还对你说什么了
mary, what else did he say to you?
我跟你说过 他喜欢你
i told you just that he liked me.
这话什么意思啊
what did he mean by that?
丽迪是一个坚强的孩子 她会没事的
liddy's a strong kid.she'll be fine.
你还好吗
are you okay?
一般吧 我不太舒服
no, dad, i'm pretty far from okay.
我们走吧
can we go?
做的不错
nice job in there.
我没开枪
i missed the shot.
你做的不错 孩子
take the compliment, son.
我说了那都是我的错
i'm saying that I was wrong about you.
我们需要单独沟通下
we need to talk alone.
我们该去大开杀戒了不然玛丽就完了
we have to kill this thing now, or mary dies.
什么 你怎么知道的
what? how do you know that?
少废话赶紧做吧
i just do, okay?
什么时候
when?
今天吧可能 或许几年后
well, maybe today, probably years from now,
但一定会发生的 相信我
but it's happening trust me.
你现在是不是变成什么先知了
so, what, are you some kind of a psychic now, too?
扯淡
no.
好吧 听我说
all right, listen to me.
现在 这个听起来有一点点
now, this is gonna sound a little…
其实 听起来挺变态的
actually, it's gonna sound massively, massively crazy.
好吧
okay.
玛丽是我母亲
mary is my mother.
你说啥
excuse me?
我是你孙子
and I am your grandson.
我知道我他妈在说什么
and I know what the hell i'm talking about.
你又想耍我是吗 孩子
you want to run that by me again, son?
我的真名是迪恩 温彻斯特
my real name is Dean winchester.
我生于1979年1月24日
i was born january 24, 1979.
我父母是玛丽和约翰 温彻斯特
my parents are mary and john winchester.
我可不听你扯淡
i don't have to listen to this.
玛丽1983年被黄眼恶魔杀害了
mary gets killed by a yellow-eyed demon in 1983.
我想说的是 今晚会发什么
now, i think that this, what happened tonight,
我觉得这是他得到她线索的时刻
i think this is the moment that he caught her scent.
我们如果不抓紧把它干掉
now, if we don't catch this thing now and kill it.
它就跑了
and it gets away…
玛丽就死了
then mary dies.
所以我在问你
so i'm asking you…
拜托
please.
你 你还好吧
y-you okay?
你答应会带我离开
you promised you'd take me away.
我当然答应了
of course I did.
那就赶紧吧
do it now.
我怎么知道库尔特手枪的事啊
how did I know about the colt, huh?
我怎么知道黄眼恶魔的事情啊
how did I know about the yellow-eyed demon.
或者还能是哪啊
or where it would be?
我可不会等这一切发生的 萨缪尔
i'm not making this up, samuel.
我身体里的每一块血肉
every bone in my body.
都准备把你打到6尺远的地方 但是
is aching to put you six feet under, but…
关于你的事情 我不能改变它
there's something about you I can't shake it.
我现在比你更抓狂了孩子 但我相信你
now, i may be crazier than you, son, but I believe you.
谢谢你
thank you.
我们怎么找到那个混蛋
how do we find this bastard?
就在这里 笔记上
right here - - the list.
用库尔特手枪
and with the colt?
是啊
yeah.
我看看
let me see it.
抱歉 我不让别人碰它
sorry.i don't let anybody hold it.
我是你爷爷
i'm your grandfather.
那也不行
nothing personal.
好吧
sure it is.
特别是你现在准备要杀我
especially when it's me you're trying to kill.
我只知道一件事
i only know one thing.
能够改变这一切的事情
that's got the juice to swing something like that.
你上头一定有人
you must have friends in high places.
所以 我杀了你妈
so, i kill your mommy?
这就是为啥你来看小时候的我
that's why you came all this way to see little ol' me?
我来这里为了干掉你
oh, i came here to kill you.
等一下
wait a minute.
如果这个愣头青娶了你妈 你
if that slug marries your mommy, are you.
你是我的一个有超能力的孩子吗
are you one of my psychic kids?
不是
no.
不是你
not you.
也许你有个妹妹
maybe you got a sis.
或者兄弟
or a bro.
太可怕了
that's terrific.
这可都解决啦
that means it all worked out.
毕竟 这是我为什么来这儿的原因
after all, it's why i'm here.
这就是你要做的交易了
so that's what this is about these deals you're making.
你不想要这些人的灵魂
you don't want these people's souls.
不想
no.
我只想要他们的孩子
i just want their children.
我来这里选择这些完美的父母
i'm here to choose the perfect parents,
像你妈妈一样
like your mommy.
为什么选她
why her?
为什么选择他们
why any of them?
因为他们纯洁而坚强
because they're strong.they're pure.
他们吃自己的粮食
they eat their wheaties.
我自己的小怪物比赛 他们是理想的牲畜
my own little master race.they're ideal breeders.
别想得这么龌龊了
oh, get your mind out of the gutter.
没人和我一起教养
no one's breeding with me.
但是玛丽
though mary…
哥们 我想做个例外
man, i'd like to make an exception.
目前为止 她是我的最爱
so far, she's my favorite.
为什么做这些交易
so, why make the deals?
我需要批准
i need permission.
我需要邀请才能进屋
i need to be invited into their houses.
我知道了 你们这些白痴靠官文指引
i know, i know the red tape will drive you nuts.
但在短短的10年里 它将证明它的价值
but in 10 short years, it'll all be worth it.
因为你知道我要对你的兄弟姐妹做什么吗
cause you know what i'm gonna do to your sibling?
我会从后面勒住他们
i'm gonna stand over their crib,
让血从他们嘴里流出来
and i'm gonna bleed into their mouth.
恶魔的血可比什么维他命矿物质强多了
demon blood is better than ovaltine, vitamins, minerals.
能让你变成肌肉壮汉
it makes you big and strong!
为什么啊
for what?
这样他们就可以领导乌合之众的恶魔军了
so they can lead your discount demon army?
这就是你的宏伟计划
is that your big plan?
拜托
please.
我的终结规划比这个要庞大多了小孩
my endgame's a hell of a lot bigger than that, kid.
终结规划 什么计划
endgame? what endgame?
我会告诉你的
like i'm gonna tell you.
或者那些坐在你肩膀上的天使会告诉你的
or those angels sitting on your shoulder.
别
no.
我会好好掩护我的行踪的
i'm gonna cover my tracks good.
你他妈想掩藏什么就掩藏什么吧
you can cover whatever the hell you want.
我还是会杀了你
i'm still gonna kill you.
好吧
right.
现在我想知道
now, that, i'd like to see.
不是今天也许
maybe not today.
看着我的眼睛 你个贱货
but you look into my eyes, you son of a bitch.
我就是那个结束你的人
'cause i'm the one that kills you.
你准备拯救每个人 对吧
so, you're gonna save everybody.is that right?
是这个意思吗
is that it?
我告诉你 有个人你不会救的
well, i'll tell you one person that you're not gonna save.
你奶奶
your grandpappy.
不要
no!
玛丽
mary.
mary!
我猜这不是个秘密
uh, I guess it's no secret.
为什么我带你出来
why I brought you way out here.
约翰
john.
因为
just…
让我进去 好吗
just let me get through this, okay?
好吧 等等
okay, wait.
约翰 你还不够了解我
there's things you don't know about me, john.
所有呢
so?
不管你是谁我都会永远爱着你的
i will always love you for exactly who you are.
我跟你说什么了老爸
what did I tell you? dad!
先生 听着
sir, just listen!
爸爸
ow! dad!
离她远点
stay away from her!
你伤着我了
you're hurting me!
放松点
hey, take it easy!
靠
no!
你杀了他
you killed him.
不仅仅是约翰 小甜心
oh, not just john, sweetie pie.
爸爸妈妈也是
mommy and daddy, too.
他们都死了
they're all dead.
不会的
no.
恐怕是这样的
yep. 'fraid so.
你现在成了小孤儿玛丽
you're little orphan mary now.
你个混蛋
you son of a bitch!
对了 棍子和石头会击碎我的骨头的哦
oh, sticks and stones may break my bones.
而且他们也不会把你家庭带回来了
and they won't bring your family back either.
我会杀了你的
i'll kill you.
我向上帝发誓
i swear to god.
咱们不要这么肉麻好不
oh, let's not get nasty.
看 我们都说了些后悔的话
now, look, we both said some things that we regret.
让我们
let's, uh…
吻别吧
kiss and make up.
我会告诉你
i'll tell you what.
我会让我的孩子恢复呼吸的
i'll arrange to have lover boy here brought back breathing.
我的父母也是吗
my parents, too?
不是
nope.
抱歉小妞 这可不在计划中
sorry, doll.that's not on the table.
你想想
think about it.
你可以永远远离猎人的生活
you could be done with hunting forever.
有白色的围栏的房子
the white picket fence,
到全国去旅行 拥有几个孩子
station wagon, couple of kids.
不在有妖怪或是恐惧
no more monsters or fear.
我可以保证这一切
i'll make sure of it.
是吗？而这一切就是要用我的灵魂来交换？
what?and all it costs is my soul?
噢 不 你可以留着你的灵魂
oh, no.you can keep your soul.
我只要一个承诺
i just need permission.
什么承诺？
for what?
嗯 十年内 我需要在你的家里呆呆
mm, in 10 years, I need to swing by your house.
为了某点事情 就这样
for a little something, that's all.
到底是什么？
for…what?
放松点
relax.
如果我的计划不被打断了
as long as i'm not interrupted,
绝对没人会受伤害
nobody gets hurt.
我保证
i promise.
否则你的余生
or you can spend the rest of your life.
将绝望而孤独
desperate and alone.
玛丽？
mary?
这可是个不错的交易
it's a good deal.
那么 成交吗？
so, what do you say?
不要！
no!
玛丽？
mary?
约翰
john.
我还是没能阻止那场交易
i couldn't stop any of it.
她还是和恶魔交易了
she still made the deal.
她还是在育儿房死了 对吧？
she still died in the nursery, didn't she?
别太勉强你自己了
don't be too hard on yourself.
你不可能阻止得了它
you couldn't have stopped it.
什么意思？
what?
命运是不可能改变的 迪恩
destiny can't be changed, Dean.
所有的挣扎最终还是导向了同样的命运
all roads lead to the same destination.
那你要让我回到过去干嘛？
then why'd you send me back?
为了真相
for the truth.
现在你知道了我们做的所有事
now you know everything we do.
该死的你究竟在说些什么
what the hell are you talking about?
萨姆去哪儿了？
where's sam?
我们都清楚亚撒色对你弟弟做了些什么
we know what azazel did to your brother.
- 但我们不知道这么做的原因 - 也不知道他想要最终的结局
- what we don't know is why - what his endgame is.
他费精心思去掩盖
he went to great lengths to cover that up.
萨姆究竟在哪儿？
where's sam?
425 霍特曼工厂
425 waterman.
你弟弟正步向危险之途 迪恩
your brother is headed down a dangerous road, Dean.
可我们去无法确定它的去向
and we're not sure where it leads.
所以 阻止他
so stop it.
否则 我们会…
or we will.